[{"answer": " Good afternoon, Im Sally", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Nice to meet you.  Im Carlos", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Good afternoon, Im Sally", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " How can I assist you today", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Nice to meet you.  Im Carlos", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Id like to get a quote for airline tickets back to Spain this summer", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": " How can I assist you today", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " All right.  What will be your departure and destination airports", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Id like to get a quote for airline tickets back to Spain this summer", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Id like to fly out of Atlanta and arrive in Madrid", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 16, "question": " All right.  What will be your departure and destination airports", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " OK.  Would you consider arriving in Barcelona if the flight was cheaper", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Id like to fly out of Atlanta and arrive in Madrid", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " No, I dont think so.  Thats too far from the town that I am going to", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " OK.  Would you consider arriving in Barcelona if the flight was cheaper", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No problem.  And what dates would you like to travel", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " No, I dont think so.  Thats too far from the town that I am going to", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " I was thinking of leaving on June 11th and returning on August 30th", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " No problem.  And what dates would you like to travel", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats a pretty long vacation", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I was thinking of leaving on June 11th and returning on August 30th", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Yes, Im a student here and we have summer vacation coming up.  Im fro", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Wow!  Thats a pretty long vacation", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " I see.  How nice.  Now, the 11th and the 30th are both Saturdays", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Yes, Im a student here and we have summer vacation coming up.  Im fro", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 34, "question": " I see.  How nice.  Now, the 11th and the 30th are both Saturdays", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Well, for example, would you be willing to leave on a weekday before th", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  Sure.  I could do that.  It wont be a problem", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Well, for example, would you be willing to leave on a weekday before th", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " OK, great.  Now, how many people will be traveling with you", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Oh, I see.  Sure.  I could do that.  It wont be a problem", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " It will be two.  My girlfriend and me", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 42, "question": " OK, great.  Now, how many people will be traveling with you", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK.  Let me check our computer here for availability of those flights.  I", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 43, "question": " It will be two.  My girlfriend and me", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  Let me check our computer here for availability of those flights.  I", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " It looks like the least expensive flight would be round trip, travelin", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Yes, I think so.  Is that a direct flight", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " It looks like the least expensive flight would be round trip, travelin", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " No, there will be one layover in Boston, Massachusetts.   Would that b", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yes, I think so.  Is that a direct flight", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Yes, one layover is OK", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 58, "question": " No, there will be one layover in Boston, Massachusetts.   Would that b", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " OK.  The price for that flight would be $450 per person.  Tax and servic", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yes, one layover is OK", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " How much extra will that be", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": " OK.  The price for that flight would be $450 per person.  Tax and servic", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " It will be an additional $150.  That includes sales tax, travel tax, and ou", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " How much extra will that be", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " So in total it would be $600 per person", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 68, "question": " It will be an additional $150.  That includes sales tax, travel tax, and ou", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " If we could have a window and middle seat on the side of the plane, that woul", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 77, "question": " So in total it would be $600 per person", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " OK.  Ill hold two seats for you on the flight until 3:00 pm tomorrow", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " If we could have a window and middle seat on the side of the plane, that woul", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Great.  Thank you.  I will let you know before 3:00 pm tomorrow if we want t", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " OK.  Ill hold two seats for you on the flight until 3:00 pm tomorrow", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Thats right", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Great.  Thank you.  I will let you know before 3:00 pm tomorrow if we want t", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " What airline is it on", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Thats right", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Air Spain", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 83, "question": " What airline is it on", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Oh, thats a good airline", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Air Spain", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Would you like me to book the flight for you today", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Oh, thats a good airline", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Well, I need to talk to my girlfriend first and check with her about the price.  Ca", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Would you like me to book the flight for you today", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I can hold them for 24 hours, after that we have to release them", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Well, I need to talk to my girlfriend first and check with her about the price.  Ca", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " OK, lets do that then.  Lets put them on hold", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I can hold them for 24 hours, after that we have to release them", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Do you have a seating preference?  Would you like aisle seats or windo", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 92, "question": " OK, lets do that then.  Lets put them on hold", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Thats fine.  Let us know if we can assist you with anything else", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Do you have a seating preference?  Would you like aisle seats or windo", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Thank you.  Bye", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Thats fine.  Let us know if we can assist you with anything else", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "09-05", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Thank you.  Bye", "qSentId": 97}]
